Wilcox College of Nursing Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Administration, undated, 1909-1997
  - Reports
    - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 47:, Folder 539)
    - Monthly Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 47:, Folder 540)
    - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 47:, Folder 541)
    - Monthly Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 47:, Folder 542)
    - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 47:, Folder 543)
    - Monthly Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 47:, Folder 544)
    - Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 47:, Folder 545)
    - Monthly Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 47:, Folder 546)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 47:, Folder 547)
    - Monthly Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 47:, Folder 548)
    - Annual Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 47:, Folder 549)
    - Monthly Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 47:, Folder 550)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 47:, Folder 551)
    - Monthly Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 47:, Folder 552)
    - Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 47:, Folder 553)
    - Monthly Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 47:, Folder 554)
    - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 47:, Folder 555)
    - Monthly Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 47:, Folder 556)
    - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 47:, Folder 557)
    - Monthly Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 47:, Folder 558)
    - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 47:, Folder 559)
    - Monthly Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 47:, Folder 560)
    - Monthly Reports, 1990 August - Septembert (Box 47:, Folder 561)
    - Notes for Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 47:, Folder 562)
  - Nursing Certification
    - Connecticut State Department of Health Services
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 48:, Folder 563)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 48:, Folder 564)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 48:, Folder 565)
      - Annual Reports, 1974-1983 (Box 48:, Folder 566)
    - MOSBY Assessment Test results, 1983-1992 (Box 48:, Folder 567)
    - MOSBY Assessment Test results, 1993-1997 (Box 48:, Folder 568)
    - NCLEX SumMarchy Profiles, 1984-1986 (Box 48:, Folder 569)
    - NCLEX SumMarchy Profiles, 1987-1988 (Box 48:, Folder 570)
    - NCLEX SumMarchy Profiles, 1989-1991 (Box 48:, Folder 571)
  - Studies / Reports
    - Skill Competencies of Wilcox Graduates, undated (Box 49:, Folder 572)
    - “3rd Annual Conference of Superintendents...” program and hand-outs, 1931 April 9 (Box 49:, Folder 573)
    - Committee on the Grading of Nursing Schools
      - Questionnaires, 1932 September (Box 49:, Folder 574)
      - Questionnaires—answered, 1932 July (Box 49:, Folder 575)
      - Study Part I, 1933 (Box 49:, Folder 576)
      - Study Part II, 1933 (Box 49:, Folder 577)
      - Study Part III, 1933 (Box 49:, Folder 578)
      - Tables, 1933 (Box 49:, Folder 579)
      - Study Part IV, 1934 March (Box 49:, Folder 580)
    - Report “A Thousand Think Together”, 1948 (Box 49:, Folder 581)
    - NLN Study- Questionnaire & letter, 1957 (Box 49:, Folder 582)
    - Graduate Nurse Questionnaire / Employer Questionnaire, 1961-1982 (Box 49:, Folder 583)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Programs Report, circa 1964 (Box 49:, Folder 584)
    - 3 Other Studies, 1964-1972 (Box 49:, Folder 585)
    - Study: Relationship of Reading Ability to state board results, 1966 (Box 49:, Folder 586)
    - Enrollment & Faculty reports to State of CT Board, 1950s (Box 49:, Folder 587)
    - Enrollment & Faculty reports to State of CT Board, 1960s (Box 49:, Folder 588)
    - Enrollment & Faculty reports to State of CT Board, 1970s (Box 50:, Folder 589)
    - Graduate Nurse Questionnaire for Advanced Ed. Results, 1972-1977 (Box 50:, Folder 590)
    - Diploma School Study
      - Statutes, executive sumMarchy and notes, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 591)
      - Press conference and consultant notes, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 592)
      - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 593)
      - “Position paper”, program examples, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 594)
      - Affiliation, Licensing and Accreditation sections, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 595)
      - Senate committee and correspondence sections, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 596)
      - Assembly of Hospital Schools of Nursing, NLN sections, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 597)
      - Other Sections, 1978-1979 (Box 50:, Folder 598)
    - Study- St. of CT Board Test Pool Examination-Statistics and Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 50:, Folder 599)
    - Student Ill Times- Questionnaire results, 1980-1981 (Box 50:, Folder 600)
    - Curriculum Committee Study on Curriculum Design, 1980-1982 (Box 51:, Folder 601)
    - Curriculum Committee questionnaire results, 1981 (Box 51:, Folder 602)
    - Recruitment of Nursing students study, 1982 (Box 51:, Folder 603)
    - Survey Analysis- User Manual & survey questions, 1982-1984 (Box 51:, Folder 604)
    - Survey Analysis- Survey results, 1982-1984 (Box 51:, Folder 605)
    - AHSN Directory of Programs & Offerings from schools, 1987 December (Box 51:, Folder 606)
    - State of CT Governor's task force on Nursing Shortage, 1988 July 28 (Box 51:, Folder 607)
    - Report of CT League of Nursing Council....4th draft, 1990 April (Box 51:, Folder 608)
    - Report “Connecticut Differential Practice Project”, 1992-1994 (Box 51:, Folder 609)
    - Applicant Profile of students, 1990-1992 (Box 51:, Folder 610)
    - Class Profile, 1989 (Box 51:, Folder 611)
    - Class Profile, 1991 (Box 51:, Folder 612)
    - Class Profile, 1992 (Box 51:, Folder 613)
    - Class Profile, 1993 (Box 51:, Folder 614)
    - Class Profile, 1994 (Box 51:, Folder 615)
    - Class Profile, 1995 (Box 51:, Folder 616)
    - Class Profile, 1996 (Box 51:, Folder 617)
    - Class Profile, 1997 (Box 51:, Folder 618)
    - Graduate Employment/ Education Survey SumMarchy, 1991-1997 (Box 51:, Folder 619)
    - Graduate Exit Interviews, 1992-1996 (Box 51:, Folder 620)
    - CT State report of Nurse Educational Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 51:, Folder 621)
    - College Level Examination Program Exam results, 1994 (Box 51:, Folder 622)
    - Study: “Comparison of Success of Students who completed the Low/ no SAT Requirement”, 1994 (Box 51:, Folder 623)
    - Educational Programs Survey- State of CT, 1996 (Box 51:, Folder 624)
    - Student program evaluations, 1967-1975 (Box 51:, Folder 625)
    - Study: Program Evaluation by students survey results, 1993-1995 (Box 51:, Folder 626)
  - Accreditation
    - NEAS&C
      - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 52:, Folder 627)
      - Application for accreditation & self study report, 1919 November (Box 52:, Folder 628)
      - Notes, 1992 (Box 52:, Folder 629)
      - Candidacy for accreditation report (drafts), 1992 April (Box 52:, Folder 630)
      - Self study report, 1992 (Box 52:, Folder 631)
      - Visit notes and visitor's report, 1993 September (Box 52:, Folder 632)
      - College Closure report, 1995 September (Box 52:, Folder 633)
    - American Nurses Credentialing Center, 1991 (Box 52:, Folder 634)
    - CT Board of Examiners for Nursing- rules & regulations, undated (Box 53:, Folder 635)
    - “Report of Survey” for Wilcox- reported to State, 1929-1941 (Box 53:, Folder 636)
    - CT Board of Examiners for Nursing
      - Correspondence, 1935-1968 (Box 53:, Folder 637)
      - Annual Reports, 1928, 1930s (Box 53:, Folder 638)
      - Annual Reports, 1940s (Box 53:, Folder 639)
      - Annual Reports, 1950s (Box 53:, Folder 640)
      - Annual Reports, 1960s (Box 53:, Folder 641)
      - Annual Reports, 1970s (Box 53:, Folder 642)
    - State of Connecticut
      - Correspondence, reports, 1975-1990 (Box 53:, Folder 643)
      - Survey Report, 1981 March 31 (Box 53:, Folder 644)
      - Faculty and Grandfathering clause, 1984-1987 (Box 53:, Folder 645)
      - Dept. of Health Services report Part I, 1985 March (Box 54:, Folder 646)
      - Dept. of Health Services report Part II, 1985 March (Box 54:, Folder 647)
      - Model for BSN Degree, 1985 October (Box 54:, Folder 648)
      - Incomplete application for accreditation, 1986 (Box 54:, Folder 649)
      - Proposal for Curriculum Revision, 1989, 1990 (Box 54:, Folder 650)
      - Application for Licensure and Accreditation, 1990 November (Box 54:, Folder 651)
      - Appendix to application, 1990 November (Box 54:, Folder 652)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1991 (Box 54:, Folder 653)
      - Notes on self-evaluation report, 1991 December (Box 54:, Folder 654)
      - Self-Evaluation report, Part I, 1991 December (Box 55:, Folder 655)
      - Self-Evaluation report, Part II, 1991 December (Box 55:, Folder 656)
      - Appendix for self-evaluation report, 1991 December (Box 55:, Folder 657)
      - Visit notes, correspondence, 1991 March - 1992 (Box 55:, Folder 658)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 55:, Folder 659)
      - Application and Progress Report, Parts A - D, 1992 September (Box 55:, Folder 660)
      - Application and Progress Reports, Parts E - M, 1992 September (Box 55:, Folder 661)
      - Announcement and Congratulations, 1993 April (Box 55:, Folder 662)
    - National League for Nursing
      - Application for Accreditation, 1939 (Box 56:, Folder 663)
      - Application for Accreditation -schedules, 1940 (Box 56:, Folder 664)
      - Report for Accreditation, 1940 October - November (Box 56:, Folder 665)
      - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 56:, Folder 666)
      - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 56:, Folder 667)
      - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 56:, Folder 668)
      - Annual Report, 1945 (Box 56:, Folder 669)
      - Re-Survey Report, 1945 September (Box 56:, Folder 670)
      - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 56:, Folder 671)
      - Re-Survey Report, 1948 February (Box 56:, Folder 672)
      - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 56:, Folder 673)
      - Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Box 56:, Folder 674)
      - Annual Report, 1949-1950 (Box 56:, Folder 675)
      - Annual Report, 1950-1951 (Box 56:, Folder 676)
      - Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Box 56:, Folder 677)
      - Application for accreditation w/ supplemental report, 1953 (Box 56:, Folder 678)
      - Re-Survey Report, 1953 June (Box 56:, Folder 679)
      - Interim Report, 1956 (Box 56:, Folder 680)
      - Policies and Procedures, 1939-1958 (Box 57:, Folder 681)
      - Policies and Procedures, 1961+ (Box 57:, Folder 682)
      - Handbooks (2), 1942, 1946 (Box 57:, Folder 683)
      - Member listing, 1941-1964 (Box 57:, Folder 684)
      - Member Agencies, 1949-1964 (Box 57:, Folder 685)
      - “Progress Report” Bulletin A.I, 1935 September (Box 57:, Folder 686)
      - “Progress Report” Bulletin C.IV, 1935 September (Box 57:, Folder 687)
      - “Progress Report” Bulletin E.I, 1935 September (Box 57:, Folder 688)
      - “Progress Report” Bulletin E.II, 1935 September (Box 57:, Folder 689)
      - “Progress Report” Bulletin E.V, 1935 September (Box 57:, Folder 690)
      - “Progress Report” Bulletin E. VIII, 1935 September (Box 57:, Folder 691)
      - Correspondence, 1939-1949 (Box 58:, Folder 692)
      - Correspondence, 1950s (Box 58:, Folder 693)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 58:, Folder 694)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 58:, Folder 695)
      - Correspondence, 1970s (Box 58:, Folder 696)
      - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 58:, Folder 697)
      - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 58:, Folder 698)
      - Application -completed, 1959 February (Box 59:, Folder 699)
      - Re-Survey Report, 1959 February (Box 59:, Folder 700)
      - Evaluation, progress report, 1959-1962 (Box 59:, Folder 701)
      - Instructions, report, 1964 (Box 59:, Folder 702)
      - Visitor's Report, 1965 March - April (Box 59:, Folder 703)
      - Visitor's Reports, 1968 October, March (Box 59:, Folder 704)
      - Self-evaluation report, 1968 March (Box 59:, Folder 705)
      - Visitor's Report, 1969 April (Box 59:, Folder 706)
      - Self-evaluation report, 1969 April (Box 59:, Folder 707)
      - Self report, evaluations, 1965-1969 (Box 59:, Folder 708)
      - Self report, 1975 February 17 (Box 60:, Folder 709)
      - Consultation visitor's report, 1975 February (Box 60:, Folder 710)
      - Self report, 1975 December 1 (Box 60:, Folder 711)
      - Notes, Plans, 1975 (Box 60:, Folder 712)
      - Special Progress Report, 1977 October 15 (Box 60:, Folder 713)
      - Nursing Consultation visit, 1980 (Box 60:, Folder 714)
      - Self-evaluation report, 1981 September (Box 60:, Folder 715)
      - Notes on visit to Wilcox, 1989 September (Box 60:, Folder 716)
      - Self-evaluation report Part I, 1989 September (Box 60:, Folder 717)
      - Self-evaluation report Part II, 1989 September (Box 60:, Folder 718)
      - Closing Report, 1992 February (Box 61:, Folder 719)
      - Site visit: correspondence and notes, 1992 June 5 (Box 61:, Folder 720)
      - Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 61:, Folder 721)
      - Self-Evaluation report Part I, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 722)
      - Self-Evaluation report Part II, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 723)
      - Self-Evaluation report Part III, 1993 (Box 61:, Folder 724)
      - Evaluation and consultation Visitor's reports, 1994 March (Box 62:, Folder 725)
      - Self-Evaluation report (rough draft) Part I, 1994 (Box 62:, Folder 726)
      - Self-Evaluation report (rough draft) Part II, 1994 (Box 62:, Folder 727)
      - Self-Evaluation report (Finalized), 1994 March (Box 62:, Folder 728)
      - Self-Evaluation report: Appendix, 1994 March (Box 62:, Folder 729)
      - Faculty Data Sheets, 1994 March (Box 62:, Folder 730)
      - SumMarchy of faculty data forms, 1994 March (Box 62:, Folder 731)
      - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 62:, Folder 732)
- Series IV: Press Materials and Photographs, undated, 1909-1997
  - Correspondence / Publications / Editorials (see also Scrapbooks)
    - Correspondence, 1910-1939 (Box 63:, Folder 733)
    - Correspondence, 1940s (Box 63:, Folder 734)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1969 (Box 63:, Folder 735)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1997 (Box 63:, Folder 736)
    - N.S.N.A. Newsletter volume III, no.1, 1956 April (Box 63:, Folder 737)
    - Vital Signs volumes, 1993-1996 (Box 63:, Folder 738)
    - Wilcox Report volumes, 1991-1993 (Box 63:, Folder 739)
    - RUSCO Commentaire Bulletin volume XIX, no.5, 1960 February (Box 63:, Folder 740)
    - Pamphlets / Booklets advertising nursing (5), 1910-1929 (Box 63:, Folder 741)
    - Brochures & Pamphlets advertising nursing (3), 1940-1959 (Box 63:, Folder 742)
    - Brochures advertising nursing (1), 1960s (Box 63:, Folder 743)
    - School Profiles, 1981-1985 (Box 63:, Folder 744)
    - Brochures, Pamphlets & Other advertisements (9), 1980s (Box 63:, Folder 745)
    - Brochures& Pamphlets(3), & advertisements (2), emblem, 1990s (Box 63:, Folder 746)
    - Editorials, undated (Box 63:, Folder 747)
    - Editorials, 1923-1983 (Box 63:, Folder 748)
    - Editorials, 1987-1992 (Box 63:, Folder 749)
    - Editorials, 1993 January - December (Box 63:, Folder 750)
    - Editorials, 1994 January - December (Box 63:, Folder 751)
    - Editorials, 1995 January - December (Box 63:, Folder 752)
    - Editorials, 1996 January - December (Box 63:, Folder 753)
    - Editorials, 1997 (Box 63:, Folder 754)
  - Scrapbooks & Notebooks
    - Volume I Notebook, 1909-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 755)
    - Newspaper Clippings from Vol. I, 1913-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 756)
    - Graduation Programs, Invites from Vol.I, 1909-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 757)
    - Ephemera from Volume I Notebook, 1909-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 758)
    - Annual Committee Reports / Minutes from Vol. I, 1909-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 759)
    - Annual Committee Reports/ Minutes from Vol. I, 1909-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 760)
    - Correspondence from Vol. I, 1909-1915 (Box 64:, Folder 761)
    - Volume II Notebook, 1915-1918 (Box 64:, Folder 762)
    - Correspondence from Vol. II, 1915-1918 (Box 64:, Folder 763)
    - Graduation Programs, Invites from Vol. II, 1915-1918 (Box 64:, Folder 764)
    - Committee Reports, Notes, Minutes from Vol. II, 1915-1918 (Box 64:, Folder 765)
    - Epehemera, Notes & Application from Vol. II, 1915-1918 (Box 64:, Folder 766)
    - Editorials from Vol. II, 1915-1918 (Box 64:, Folder 767)
    - Volume III Notebook, 1918-1922 (Box 64:, Folder 768)
    - Committee Reports / Minutes from Vol. III, 1918-1922 (Box 64:, Folder 769)
    - Editorials from Vol. III, 1918-1922 (Box 64:, Folder 770)
    - Correspondence, Notes from Vol. III, 1918-1922 (Box 64:, Folder 771)
    - Volume IV Notebook, 1922-1924 (Box 65:, Folder 772)
    - Editorials from Vol. IV, 1922-1924 (Box 65:, Folder 773)
    - Correspondence from Vol. IV, 1917-1924 (Box 65:, Folder 774)
    - Graduation Programs, Invites from Vol. IV, 1923-1928 (Box 65:, Folder 775)
    - Committee Reports / Epehmera from Vol. IV, 1922-1924 (Box 65:, Folder 776)
    - Gift Book, 1931-1960 (Box 65:, Folder 777)
    - Alumni Association Editorials from Scrapbook IV, 1948-1978 (Box 65:, Folder 778)
    - Alumni Association Invites & Tickets from Scrapbook IV, 1948-1978 (Box 65:, Folder 779)
    - Alumni Notes from Scrapbook IV, 1948-1978 (Box 65:, Folder 780)
    - Alumni Newsletters & Updates from Scrapbook IV, 1948-1978 (Box 65:, Folder 781)
    - Scrapbook I & II: Glee Club, Play & other Programs, 1930-1959 (Box 66:, Folder 782)
    - Pamphlets from Scrapbooks, 1960-1979 (Box 66:, Folder 783)
    - Class Books from Scrapbooks, 1946-1969 (Box 66:, Folder 784)
    - News Publication from Scrapbook, 1945-1946 (Box 66:, Folder 785)
    - Correspondence from Scrapbooks, 1930-1950s (Box 66:, Folder 786)
    - Wedding Invitations from Scrapbook I, 1940-1950 (Box 66:, Folder 787)
    - Wedding Invitations from Scrapbook II, 1950-1960 (Box 66:, Folder 788)
    - Wedding Invitations from Scrapbook III, 1960-1979 (Box 66:, Folder 789)
    - Baby Announcements from Scrapbook I, 1930-1949 (Box 66:, Folder 790)
    - Alumnae Banquet Invitations / Programs from Scrapbooks, 1937-1962 (Box 66:, Folder 791)
    - Alumnae Invitations / Programs from Scrapbooks, 1960-1979 (Box 66:, Folder 792)
    - Graduation Programs from Scrapbooks, 1910-1939 (Box 66:, Folder 793)
    - Graduation Programs from Scrapbooks, 1940-1959 (Box 66:, Folder 794)
    - Graduation Programs & related documents from Scrapbooks, 1960s-1980 (Box 66:, Folder 795)
    - Graduation Invitations from Scrapbooks, 1933-1959 (Box 66:, Folder 796)
    - Graduation Invitations from Scrapbooks, 1960-1979 (Box 66:, Folder 797)
    - Class Yearbook -pieces only from Scrapbooks, 1929 (Box 67:, Folder 798)
    - Class Yearbook -pieces only from Scrapbooks, 1941 (Box 67:, Folder 799)
    - Class Yearbook -pieces only from Scrapbooks, 1948 (Box 67:, Folder 800)
    - Class Yearbook- pieces only from Scrapbooks, 1949 (Box 67:, Folder 801)
    - Ephemera from Scrapbooks I, II, III, 1930-1979 (Box 67:, Folder 802)
    - Engagement / Wedding Announcements from Scrapbook I, 1941-1943 (Box 67:, Folder 803)
    - Engagement / Wedding Announcements from Scrapbook II, 1950-1966 (Box 67:, Folder 804)
    - Engagement / Wedding Announcements from Scrapbook III, 1960s (Box 67:, Folder 805)
    - Death / Funeral Announcements from Scrapbooks I-III, 1940-1968 (Box 67:, Folder 806)
    - Editorials Scrapbook I, 1930-1949 (Box 67:, Folder 807)
    - Editorials Scrapbook I, 1930-1959 (Box 67:, Folder 808)
    - Editorials Scrapbook I, 1930-1959 (Box 67:, Folder 809)
    - Editorials Scrapbook II, 1952-1958 (Box 67:, Folder 810)
    - Editorials Scrapbook II, 1959-1966 (Box 67:, Folder 811)
    - Editorials Scrapbook II, 1960s (Box 67:, Folder 812)
    - Editorials Scrapbook III, 1960s (Box 67:, Folder 813)
    - Editorials Scrapbook III, 1970-1987 (Box 67:, Folder 814)
  - Scrapbook Photographs
    - Middlesex Memorial Hospital, 1910 (Box 68:, Folder 815)
    - Miss Boland & Mr. Dwyer, circa 1910 (Box 68:, Folder 816)
    - Nurses in Queue, 1914 (Box 68:, Folder 817)
    - Hendley Hall: Miss Sharp, Miss Hyde, Miss Crescimmo, circa 1922 (Box 68:, Folder 818)
    - Hendley Memorial Hall, circa 1920 (Box 68:, Folder 819)
    - Operating Room: Miss Hyde, Miss Lund, Miss Anderson, 1914 (Box 68:, Folder 820)
    - 11 Photos from Scrapbook I, 1909-1920 (Box 68:, Folder 821)
    - 11 Photos from Scrapbook I, 1930s (Box 68:, Folder 822)
    - 18 Photos from Scrapbook I, 1940s (Box 68:, Folder 823)
    - Class Photos (2), 1944 (Box 68:, Folder 824)
    - Class Photo, 1945 (Box 68:, Folder 825)
    - Class Photo, 1951 (Box 68:, Folder 826)
    - “Tea”, 1951 (Box 68:, Folder 827)
    - School Photo, 1956 (Box 68:, Folder 828)
    - (16) Various Photos -see backs for details, 1950-1954 (Box 68:, Folder 829)
    - Class Photo, circa 1950 (Box 68:, Folder 830)
    - 5 Photos: Christmas Caroling, Christmas Bazaar, 1956 December (Box 68:, Folder 831)
    - Individual Class Photos, 1956 (Box 68:, Folder 832)
    - Miss Connecticut Beauty Pageant, 1958 (Box 68:, Folder 833)
    - (4) Photos of the Annual Nurses Dance, circa 1958 (Box 68:, Folder 834)
    - Individual Class Photos, 1958 (Box 68:, Folder 835)
    - 17 Photographs, 1955-1959 (Box 68:, Folder 836)
    - Miss Goodrich & Miss Hyde, circa 1960 (Box 68:, Folder 837)
    - Individual Class Photos, 1960 (Box 68:, Folder 838)
    - Individual Class Photos, 1961 (Box 68:, Folder 839)
    - Individual Class Photos, 1962 (Box 68:, Folder 840)
    - Class Photo, 1963 (Box 68:, Folder 841)
    - Class Photo, 1964 (Box 68:, Folder 842)
    - Class Photo, 1965 (Box 68:, Folder 843)
    - Class Photo, 1967 (Box 68:, Folder 844)
    - 21 Photos: DOctoberor's & Seniors Basketball Game, 1967 (Box 68:, Folder 845)
    - 11 Photos: Construction, Nurses & Buildings, 1968 (Box 68:, Folder 846)
    - Class Photo, 1968 (Box 68:, Folder 847)
    - (2) Ona M. Wilcox Testimonial Dinner, 1970 July 9 (Box 68:, Folder 848)
    - 5 Photos, 2 Negatives, circa 1970 (Box 68:, Folder 849)
    - 19 Photos: from Scrapbook III -Graduation?, 1980s (Box 68:, Folder 850)
  - Photographs (not from Scrapbooks)
    - 29 Photos & negatives of Christmas Party, undated (Box 69:, Folder 851)
    - 16 Photographs of Party, undated (Box 69:, Folder 852)
    - (8) Photos -Employees, undated (Box 69:, Folder 853)
    - Mrs. E. Hershey Smeath & Col. Herbert L. Camp, undated (Box 69:, Folder 854)
    - Children's ward, undated (Box 69:, Folder 855)
    - (2) Photos- children's ward, undated (Box 69:, Folder 856)
    - Hospital Volunteers / Ambulance, undated (Box 69:, Folder 857)
    - Pressing Uniforms, undated (Box 69:, Folder 858)
    - The Braum Masseur Whirlpool Machine, undated (Box 69:, Folder 859)
    - Class officers, 1955 (Box 69:, Folder 860)
    - Dr. Barton, undated (Box 69:, Folder 861)
    - Unidentified man, undated (Box 69:, Folder 862)
    - Woman feeding baby, undated (Box 69:, Folder 863)
    - Interior of House, undated (Box 69:, Folder 864)
    - Hospital (front view), undated (Box 69:, Folder 865)
    - 3 Photos of public speaker - Henry Lyman, circa 1953 (Box 69:, Folder 866)
    - Operating Room, undated (Box 69:, Folder 867)
    - Office of the Controller - Mr. Starks, undated (Box 69:, Folder 868)
    - Cooking in the Kitchen, undated (Box 69:, Folder 869)
    - Middlesex Hospital- first addition, undated (Box 69:, Folder 870)
    - 2 Photos- singing at the piano, undated (Box 69:, Folder 871)
    - Nurse assisting patient, undated (Box 69:, Folder 872)
    - Photograph of Nurse, undated (Box 69:, Folder 873)
    - Nurse welcoming student, undated (Box 69:, Folder 874)
    - College dorm room, undated (Box 69:, Folder 875)
    - Cedar Crest Auditorium, undated (Box 69:, Folder 876)
    - Rita Fornier, x-ray technician, undated (Box 69:, Folder 877)
    - Nursery, undated (Box 69:, Folder 878)
    - Sterilization of enameled utensils, undated (Box 69:, Folder 879)
    - X-Ray, undated (Box 69:, Folder 880)
    - Respiratory Therapy, undated (Box 69:, Folder 881)
    - (2) Male Employees (Doctors?), undated (Box 69:, Folder 882)
    - Male employees, undated (Box 69:, Folder 883)
    - Nurses aides (?), undated (Box 69:, Folder 884)
    - Nurses and Nuns, undated (Box 69:, Folder 885)
    - Middlesex Hospital- East New Wing, 1910 (Box 69:, Folder 886)